{
    "subject": "Andrew_II_of_Hungary",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Gertrude_of_Merania",
    "human_readable": "Andrew II of Hungary is married to Gertrude of Merania.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9586600661277771,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Andrew II of Hungary and Gertrude of Merania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.950896143913269,
            "question": "Is Andrew II of Hungary married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9461126923561096,
            "question": "To whom was Andrew II of Hungary married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9315099716186523,
            "question": "Name the wife of Andrew II of Hungary."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.929023027420044,
            "question": "Who is married to Gertrude of Merania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9197642803192139,
            "question": "Who is Gertrude of Merania married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9147958159446716,
            "question": "Who was the wife of Andrew II of Hungary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8590465188026428,
            "question": "With whom did Andrew II of Hungary enter a marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8315295577049255,
            "question": "What is the name of Andrew II of Hungary's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.807158350944519,
            "question": "What is the name of Andrew II of Hungary's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Andrew II of Hungary is married to Gertrude of Merania.",
            "html": "yago_26760_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Andrew II of Hungary's wife?",
            "html": "yago_26760_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=With whom did Andrew II of Hungary enter a marriage?",
            "html": "yago_26760_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the wife of Andrew II of Hungary?",
            "html": "yago_26760_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26760_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Gertrude of Merania was the first wife of King Andrew II of Hungary and that they had five children together."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Gertrude of Merania was the first wife of King Andrew II of Hungary, which supports the statement that Andrew II of Hungary is married to Gertrude of Merania."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}